ahrn.com 2016-11-27

# AHRN.com | Connecting the military community with housing

### Our Privacy Policy

Welcome to the Automated Housing Referral Network (AHRN.com). By visiting this website, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use or access this site. 

You can visit the website without revealing who you are or providing any personal information about yourself. This website DOES NOT place persistent cookies on your personal computer. This website may use session cookies to deliver a customized interface for each user. 

You should be aware that we collect page hit statistics when you visit the website, that may include information about you, which helps us understand how the site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of a stay at the website, etc. 

If you register at this website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your username and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your username or password. 

There will be times, such as when you self-register or register properties in the website database, when we will need to obtain personally identifiable information from you or about you. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, your rank (if in the Military), your business address, etc. The information we receive about you or from you may be used by us and others to help process or complete a transaction related to housing referrals on this website; to comply with any law, regulation, audit or court order; to help improve our website or the products or services we offer; for research; to better understand our customers' needs; to develop new offerings; and to alert you to new products and services in which you may be interested. As a matter of policy, we do not sell, rent or share any of your personal information, including your email address, to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. 

We safeguard your information using known security standards and procedures. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, AHRN.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from the website, and you do so at your own risk. 

Under some circumstances we may require financial information, including credit card information to process user initiated credit card transactions for fee related services. All financial transactions are processed via a secure, PCI compliant interface. 

#### Communications from the Site

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals and promotions, as well as newsletters. You are signed up for these emails upon registration and may unsubscribe at any time by going to the My Account tab and opting out of the emails, or by following the unsubscribe directions included in the email. 

From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on the website. If you choose to participate, we may request certain personal information, including your email address. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you have the choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information. We will not share the personal information provided through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

Based upon the personal information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your email address, username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. Email is the primary means of communication on the site and you must be able to receive this information to use properly. 

#### Legal Requests

AHRN.com cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights, to help protect users from illegal activities. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, city, state, telephone number, email address, UserID history, fraud complaints, and listing history without a subpoena. Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to: prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or report suspected illegal activity. 

Please be aware that we may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to e-mail your questions to us at [ahrnsupport@ahrn.com](mailto:ahrnsupport@ahrn.com;ahrnsupport@marcoa.com). 

**Updated: 6/12/14**
